JOMEL ISIDRO

+639273221531

iomelisidro.1998@gmail.com
 iomelisidro.1998@gmail.com

Sta Rita Olongapo City



FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

I am a graduate of Bachelor of Science in Information and Technology with good experience in website development. I have 2yrs experience as a web developer with a vast array of knowledge in different programming languages and database administration. I also experienced develop a desktop applications. Seeking opportunities to leverage analysis, problem-solving, complex algorithms, and website development experience in a challenging role as a full-stack developer.

SKILLS

FRONT-END	BACK-END	FRAMEWORKS	OTHERS
■ HTML	■ PHP	■ Laravel/Lumen	■ Github
CSS / Bootstrap	Node JS	■ Vue JS	Cpanel
Javascript / Jquery	Mysql	Angular Typescript	■ FTP

EDUCATION

Gordon College Olongapo City, Philippines

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Major in Web Development, 2016-2021

EXPERIENCE

IFormatlogic I.T. Solutions - Nov 2020 - Jan 2022

Full-stack Web Developer

- Creates a system using Javascript, jQuery and Laravel Frameworks
- Creating new websites and maintaining existing websites
- Work with data analyst and client to meet the project requirements.
- Follow schedules and deliverables set by the project manager / client.
- Perform and commit projects into the GIT repository.
- Perform and upload a project into the cPanel hosting server.
- Analyze complex algorithms and problem solving about the website projects.

Cylix Technologies - May 2022 - Feb 2023

Full-stack Web Developer

- Creates a system using Vue JS and Laravel Frameworks
- Use SQLYOG for managing the database.
- Improving and creating new functionalities of the ERP website.
- Perform and commit projects into the GIT repository.
- Helping the team for the new enhancement of the system.
- Work with the team and project manager to meet the project requirements